# Steven Bi

## **Full Stack Developer**

Perth WA 6107 steven.bb.0221@gmail.com +61 450 980 608

To summarize, I am a qualified software engineer base in Perth currently working as a full-stack web developer. Passionate about web app development with years of experiences in programming Python / Node.js on server side, and React / Vue for UI implementation.

Also, I am comfortable with Django / FastApi / Express in AWS environment, practical experiences with data visualization tools. Such as DeckGl / Mapbox / D3.js / Three.js.

#### Personal Details

Eligible to work in Australia: Yes

Highest Level of Education: Bachelor Degree

## Work Experience

### **Full Stack Developer**

Pointerra - Perth WA June 2022 to Present

Work on the main product Pointerra core and potal site which is a collaborative user management tool that grants accessibility across the enterprise ensuring all business units can discover and exploit the 3D point clouds data info. (Vue & Django & Node js & AWS)

- Maintain platform reliability, scalability, and robustness improvements
- Helping deployment process for Pointerra's SaaS applications,
- Managing and improving the automated software build and test platform for frontend system

#### **Software Developer**

Atomorphis - Perth WA November 2020 to April 2022

Working on a primary in house product 'Gemini' which is an agent based simulation for helping to identify bottlenecks and plan in mining project, as well as maintain other exist products such as excel & python based data modeling tool. (React, MUI, Mapbox, FastApi, Docker, )

- Implement interactive and map based front-end system from scratch
- Finished & delivered a fully functional Gemini prototype.

- Continuously work on Gemini data visualization of mining fleet and equipment simulation in 2D & 3D.
- API development
- Dockerize and maintain whole front-end sytem in docker container

### **Web Developer (Contract)**

South Pacific Union Group - Bunbury WA July 2020 to November 2020

Short contract with a local chain hotel in Bunbury, rebuild hotel website, restore history both db and excel data, maintain hotel room booking services. (Python, Wordpress, Html, Css, Js)

- Restore website and its data from the damaged backup & online booking system
- Excel based data analysis tool
- Off-line email marketing system

#### **Software Developer**

Lianjia (https://sh.lianjia.com/) - Shang Hai January 2019 to April 2020

Work on one of the largest realestate online platform in Shang Hai, China, helping and linking between tanants and property owners / agents. (React, Redux, Cypress, Python, Alibaba Cloud)

- Maintain online platform and bug fix
- End to end test
- Work on new features and UI improvement

#### Education

### **Bachelor of Science (Computing) in Software Engineering**

Curtin University - Perth WA

August 2014 to December 2018

#### Skills

- JS & React & Node (3 years)
- Python & API Development (3 years)
- Html & Css (3 years)
- Material UI (3 years)
- Git & Docker (3 years)
- Mapbox & DeckGL (2 years)
- Postgres (2 years)

- Django & FastApi (2 years)
- Pyxl (1 year)

## Links

https://chen-bbe.github.io/MyPage/

https://github.com/Chen-BBe/

## Certifications and Licenses

## **SCJP**

2010 to 2012

Sun Certified Java Programmer

## Additional Information

• Language: Mandarin and English